Turn the page. Start a new chapter.
Tumbledown is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Sean Mewshaw.
A young woman struggles to move on with her life after the death of her husband, an acclaimed folk singer, when a
brash New York writer forces her to confront her loss and the ambiguous circumstances of his death.
Hannah Miles, played by Rebecca Hall.
Andrew McCabe, played by Jason Sudeikis.
Finley, played by Dianna Agron.
Ellen Jespersen, played by Blythe Danner.
Upton, played by Griffin Dunne.
Curtis, played by Joe Manganiello.
Tumbledown is a 2015 American romantic comedy drama film directed by Sean Mewshaw, written by Desiree
Van Til, and starring Rebecca Hall, Jason Sudeikis, Dianna Agron and Joe Manganiello.
It was released on February 5, 2016, by Starz Digital.
The film explores themes of widow, biography, writer, folk singer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.